

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Details

St. Petersburgo St. Petersburgo, 197227 Russian Federation +79623317132 mariojorge1997@mail.ru

NATIONALITY

Angolan

DRIVING LICENSE

Not

DATE / PLACE OF BIRTH

29/11/1997

Luanda

Links

Github

LinkedIn

Stackoverflow

Personal project

Skills

React

HTML5

JavaScript

CSS3

Tailwindcss

TypeScript

Reactjs

Nodejs

Git

GitHub

Profile

Hello! I am a web developer with JS and Typescript. In my daily life I use frameworks and tools like React, Next, Tailwind, Styled-Components etc, in addition to learn new things in the JS ecosystem and reading books (clean code, Smarter way to learn JS and JS the definitive guide) to become a better programmer every day. Now I'm focusing to be JavaScript expert developer.

Employment History

Web developer, 87LABS LLC, Remote work

JANUARY 2020 - JANUARY 2022

87LABS LLC is a technology consulting company with offices in the US, the Netherlands and Brazil. I also contributed to the development of the company's Design System. My daily life was composed of technologies such as: Reactjs and Tailwind.

Web developer, LetsEvents, Remote work

JANUARY 2020 - APRIL 2021

I joined Lets through 87Labs which is a programming consultancy. Lets was the best company I've had the pleasure of working so far. At Lets, my daily life was composed of technologies such as: Reactjs, Nextjs, GraphQI, Apollo Client, Tailwind and Storybook.

Web developer, Leroy Merlin, Remote work

MAY 2021 - JANUARY 2022

I joined Leroy through 87Labs which is a programming consultancy. At Leroy Merlin, my daily life consisted of the following technologies: Reactjs, TypeScript, Storybook, Git and Github, Css with Emotion.

Web developer, Seasoned, Remote work

OCTOBER 2021 - PRESENT

At seasoned, I work as a front-end developer, acting as front-end team leader for one of the projects. My responsibility within the team, is to understand about the new features, break those features into smaller tasks, ensure that everything is clear to other developers, program and ensure that each feature is delivered on time and with quality.

Education

bachelor degree, St. Petersburg State Electrotechnical University, Saint Petersburg

SEPTEMBER 2019 - AUGUST 2023

Courses

EPIC REACT, KENT C. DODDS

NOVEMBER 2021 - FEBRUARY 2022

TESTING JAVASCRIPT, KENT C. DODDS

APRIL 2022 - MAY 2022

RESPONSIVE WEB DESIGN CERTIFICATION, FREE CODE CAMP

MAY 2022 - JUNE 2022

JAVASCRIPT ALGORITHMS AND DATA STRUCTURES, FREE CODE CAMP

JUNE 2022 - AUGUST 2022

Remix	
Language	es
Portuguese	
English	
Russian	

Hobbies

In addition to my passion for programming, I also love hanging out with friends and my girlfriend, hanging out with family on the weekend, reading books, working out and playing game.

Take a look at my UI Library: https://github.com/Mario-aj/maj-ui

REACTJS AND NODEJS, ROCKETSEAT

JULY 2020 - NOVEMBER 2020

TYPESCRIPT, ROCKETSEAT

NOVEMBER 2021 - JANUARY 2022